https://www.enovate.co.uk/privacy

EnovateMake an enquiry01245 64 64 64This agreement was last modified on 21st August 2018.Table of ContentsWhat information do we collect about you?How will we use your data?What marketing communications do we send?What is our legal basis for processing data?Will we share this information with others?How do we protect the security of personal data?How long do we keep your data for?What are your privacy rights?How do you make a compliant?How will we let you know of changes to our privacy policy?How should you contact us?What cookies does the Website use and what is their purpose? (Our Cookie Notice)What are web cookies?Why do we use cookies?What cookies do we use?Website cookie acceptanceTurning cookies offUpdating our Cookie NoticeEnovate Design Ltd, trading as Enovate ("us", "we", or "our") operates https://www.enovate.co.uk/ (the "Website").We are committed to protecting your privacy and will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully and in accordance with data protection legislation.This privacy policy is intended to give you an understanding of how and why we use the information you provide to us both via the Website and otherwise.Please feel free to contact us regarding any questions relating to this privacy policy.Back to topWhat information do we collect about you?We collect personal data about you for a number of reasons, including communicating with you and responding to requests for information.The personal data we collect can include:your full name;job title;email address;telephone number(s);records of your correspondence with us;information you may enter onto the Website; andother information you share with us.We also collect information about the use of our Website using cookies (see the "Cookies Notice" section below for more information).We also collect information about your computer hardware and software, which can include: your IP address, the web browser you use (e.g. Google Chrome, etc.), access times and referring websites. We use this information for the operation of the service, to maintain and improve the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the Website.Back to topHow will we use your data?We will process your data for the following reasons:To deliver services and information you have requested from us;To contact you about potential career opportunities at Enovate (if you have registered your interest in a position at Enovate);To send you updates about our work, Enovate news, and general industry developments (if you have agreed to receive them);For our own internal administrative purposes and to keep a record of your relationship with us;To manage your communication preferences;To conduct surveys, research and gather feedback;To produce reports and studies based upon our activities (only anonymised data);To comply with applicable laws and regulations, and requests from statutory agencies.Back to topWhat marketing communications do we send?For those that have agreed to receive it, we send a quarterly newsletter, which contains updates about our work, Enovate news and general industry news and developments. The purpose of these communications is to keep you abreast of changes within the field of website design and development, and digital marketing.You can opt-out or update your communication preferences at any time by using the details in the "Contact Us" section below. Any electronic communications will have a link to unsubscribe from future electronic communications, so you can manage your own consent.If you tell us you do not wish to receive marketing communications, you may still receive administrative communications.Back to topWhat is our legal basis for processing data?We must have a lawful basis for collecting and using personal data under data protection law and we are required to let you know the lawful basis on which we rely to process your personal data:Obtaining your consent to use your data for a particular purpose (for example to send you our email newsletter, to notify you of potential career opportunities or to collect sensitive personal data);Where we need to process your data in order to perform our obligations under a contract that we have entered into with you (for example to deliver services); andTo process data where we are under a legal obligation to do so.Back to topWill we share this information with others?We do not share, sell or rent your information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will not otherwise disclose your personal information unless required to do so by a regulatory agency or law.We may allow our staff, consultants and/or external providers (data processors) acting on our behalf to access and use your information for the purposes for which you have provided to us (e.g. to analyse data and to process payments). We only provide them with the information they need to deliver the relevant service, and ensure that we take steps to ensure that they process personal data in a secure manner.Back to topHow do we protect the security of personal data?We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal information from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed.While we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal data, you acknowledge that the use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data transferred via the internet. If you have any particular concerns about your information, please contact us.We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data security breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected breach where we are legally required to do so.The information we collect from you will not be transferred to and processed and/or stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA").Back to topHow long do we keep your data for?We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal information so that it can no longer be associated with you, in which case we may use such information without further notice to you. Once you no longer have a relationship with us, we will retain and securely destroy your personal information in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.If you request to receive no further contact from us, we will keep some basic information about you on our suppression list in order to avoid sending you unwanted communications in the future.Back to topWhat are your privacy rights?You have the right to know what information we hold about you and to ask, in writing, to see your records. We will provide you with details of the records we hold as soon as possible and at latest within one month, unless the request is complex. We may require proof of identity before we are able to release the data. Please use the details in the "Contact Us" section below if you would like to exercise this right.You have the right to be informed how your personal data will be used. This policy as well as any additional information or notice that is provided to you either at the time you provided your details, or otherwise, is intended to provide you with this information.Where we process your data on the basis of your consent (for example, to send you our email newsletter) you can withdraw that consent at any time. To do this, or to discuss this right further with us, please contact us using the details in the "Contact us" section below.In some cases, you have the right to be forgotten (i.e. to have your personal data deleted from our database). Where you have requested that we do not send you marketing communications we will need to keep some limited information in order to ensure that you are not contacted in the future.If you believe our records are inaccurate you have the right to ask for those records concerning you to be updated. To update your records please get in touch with us using the details in the "Contact us" section below.Where we are processing your personal data because you have given us your consent to do so, you have the right to request that the data is transferred from one service provider to another.Back to topHow do you make a compliant?If you are unhappy with the way in which we have handled your personal data please contact us using the details below. You are also entitled to make a complaint to the Information Commissioner's Office.Back to topHow will we let you know of changes to our privacy policy?We may update this policy from time to time without notice to you, so please check it regularly. We will however aim to bring any significant changes to your attention.Back to topHow should you contact us?Please contact us using the details on our contact us page if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you.Back to topWhat cookies does the Website use and what is their purpose? (Our Cookie Notice)This Cookie Notice explains how we use cookies and other tracking technologies through our Website.This Cookies Notice is to be read alongside our Privacy Policy which explains how we use personal information. If you do not accept our use of cookies please disable them within your web browser following our guidance below.Back to topWhat are web cookies?Web cookies are small text files, that are placed on your computer or mobile device by a website when you visit it. Cookies store information related to your session on a website and are often used to record your preferences or distinguish you from other users of the website. Cookies are useful and sometimes essential to the functionality of a website. Like most websites, we use cookies.Although this Cookies Notice refers to the general term "cookie", which is the main method used by this Website to store information, a web browser's local storage space is also used for the same purpose and we may use other tracking technologies through this website such as web beacons. As a result, the information included in this Cookie Policy is likewise applicable to all such tracking technologies that we use.Back to topWhy do we use cookies?To make the website function: For example cookies enable you to log in to our website.To collect anonymous statistics: The information collected by cookies enables us to improve the website through usage figures and patterns.To improve your experience: For example to prevent you having to re-enter details when you have already done so.Measuring how cost-effective our advertising is: Cookies are used to help us see how many people who click our adverts go on to do something further and to help make advertising content more relevant to your interests.Back to topWhat cookies do we use?The table below provides more information about the cookies and other tracking technologies we use and why:Name of cookieOwnerPurposeExpiresCraftSessionIdEnovateUsed to allow user login (Craft CMS)At end of sessioncookieconsent_statusEnovateStores acceptance of our cookie consent notice1 year_gaGoogleUsed to distinguish users (Google Analytics)2 years_gidGoogleUsed to distinguish users (Google Analytics)24 hours_gat_<property-id>GoogleUsed to throttle request rate (Google Analytics)1 minutegwccGoogleUsed to track call conversions (Google AdWords)3 months__cfduidCloudFlareUsed for click fraud prevention (ClickCease)1 yearMUIDMicrosoft BingUsed to distinguish users (Bing Ads)15 monthsMUIDBMicrosoft BingUsed to distinguish users (Bing Ads)15 monthsfrFacebookUsed to distinguish users (Facebook)3 monthsBizoIDLinkedInUsed by LinkedIn insights and ads tags1 monthlang (x 2)LinkedInUsed by LinkedIn for tracking the use of embedded services.At end of sessionlidcLinkedInUsed by LinkedIn for tracking the use of embedded services.At end of sessionUserMatchHistoryLinkedInUsed for display advertising via LinkedIn network1 monthbcookieLinkedInUsed by LinkedIn for tracking the use of embedded services.2 yearsbscookieLinkedInUsed by LinkedIn for tracking the use of embedded services.2 yearsBack to topWebsite cookie acceptanceBy clicking the option to continue to browse our Website when you first visited the Website you have consented to our use of cookies as updated from time to time. In particular, you consent to cookies being stored on your computer and/or mobile device (unless rejected or disabled by your browser).Back to topTurning cookies offWeb browsers allow cookies by default but can easily be disallowed. It you do not accept our use of cookies please configure your browser to disallow cookies from our Website. However, you should be aware that this may disable some functionality of the website that is reliant upon cookies. The option to do this is usually found in the options, settings or preferences menu of your browser or mobile device.Back to topUpdating our Cookie NoticeWe may update our use of cookies from time to time and consequently we may update this Cookies Notice. We therefore recommend that you review this Cookies Notice regularly.
Home
Portfolio
Services
About
Blog
Contact
Facebook
Twitter
